Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Woman] Do you know
the expression ''a man's man'' ?
A man's man
is the leader of the pack.
The kind of man other men
look up to, admire and emulate.
A man's man
is the kind of man who...
[Chuckles] just doesn 't get
what women are about.
Nick, my ex-husband,
is the ultimate man's man.
I probably never
should have married him.
I don't think he understood
a thing about me.
So, this is Nick Marshall's office.
Wanna peek ?
Don't worry.
He never gets in before 10:00.
He'll send you on more errands than
anyone in the entire company...
'cause he can't do
anything for himself.
He's the least politically
correct guy in the universe.
He's the king of all
the T and A ads we do.
You want babes in bikinis ?
He's your man.
My dad ? How can I
best describe him ?
He's always been...
like an uncle to me.
Yeah, Uncle Dad.
Although,
Nick was a charmer.
Completely irresistible
at first,
which feeds into
the whole ''man's man'' thing.
You know about
Nick's mother, right ?
Because once you understand
about Nick's mother,
you understand Nick.
[Woman] Nick was actually
born and raised in Las Vegas.
Nick's mother was a real,
honest-to-God Las Vegas showgirl.
When otherboys were outside
riding their bikes and playing ball,
Nick was backstage
hanging with the girls.
He was their mascot,
their little pet.
They couldn 't get enough
of those baby blues.
- Bang ! Bang !
- [ Laughs ]
lf you ask me, I'd say Nick's
mother just about killed it...
for every woman
Nick would ever meet.
She had a lot of sugardaddies
in her life,
but only one true love--
the boy
with the family jewels.
17, 18, 19, 20.
Let me see that, kid.
And since Nick
didn 't have a father,
his mom made sure he was always
surrounded by strong role models.
- Come here, huh ?
- [ Screams ]
- Men her boy could look up to.
- Now you're ready, huh ?
Keep countin', kid.
There was nothing normal about
the way Nick Marshall was raised.
So, what can you expect ?
You don't have to be Freud
to figure out...
this was one cockeyed way
to enter the world.
[ Groaning ]
Oh !
Don't you ever knock ?
It's almost 10:00. You gotta go
to work, and I gotta vacuum in here.
And don't forget - Another one
who wears vanilla perfume.
Don't you know any women
who don't want to smell like candy ?
- Toss me my lighter, babe ?
- Babe ?
What am I,
a little pig ?
I don't have time
to make you no onion bagel,
so please do not start
to beg, okay ?
And for the record, l don't like
finding these things in your sofa.
What kind of woman
wears underwear like this ?
Hey, my mother wore
underwear like that.
Just put them somewhere,
will you, babe ?
Well, ''babe'' is gonna put it
in the trash where it belongs.
- So, your mother should excuse me.
- [ Sighs ]
Did you ever consider dating
a woman who wears real underwear?
The kind that covers the entire
bottom the way it's supposed to ?
- No. But if I do, should I call ?
- Oh !
I'm gonna go clean
the kitchen.
You couldn't toast me
a little bagel, could you ?
Light cream cheese, tomatoes.
Capers if we have any.
Please! Come on.
l can't think on an empty stomach.
Okay. Allright. But only because
you didn 't call me that pig name.
Okay, you got it, babe.
Mr. Marshall,
how are you doing today ?
- I'm fit as a dancing bear.
- I'll get that cab for you.
- [ Whistles ]
- That's some set of pipes you got.
- You have an excellent day, sir.
- And you.
At ease.
- [ Gasps ]
- Oh, oh, I'm so sorry !
I absolutely
did not mean to do that.
- Here. Let me get that for you.
- It's okay.
No, I'm mortified.
I can see your hands are full.
- Thank you.
- Sorry. Let me get the door.
[ Grunts ]
- [ Giggles ] Thank you.
- Thank you.
Halfcup, grande, nonfat,
thick foam, wet cap, no lid.
''Halfcaff,'' grande, nonfat,
- So, when do you find out ?
- Um, today, I think.
Unless I didn't get it, and then
I will just never find out.
I'm sure I didn't get it. They were
looking for an ''earth mother'' type.
I overheard the director
say I was more space cadet.
I'm an actress.
I can be whatever you want.
- Is that true, can you ?
- Oh, better be true.
Otherwise, I'm stuck playing ditsy
coffee girl the rest of my life.
Thank you.
Hon ? Thanks.
Oh ! Hi, Nick. Hi.
Oh, Lola, my love. When are you
gonna let me buy you dinner ?
Nick, I don't know why you don't
believe me. I'm not your type.
Trust me on this one. Cappuccino,
extra foam. Tall or grande ?
Grande. Or at least
I like to think so.
- Next.
- You know, rumor has it...
I'm getting some really
big news at work today.
At least come out with me.
Celebrate. I'll buy you a coffee.
Memo to you:
I work in a coffee shop.
Hi. What can I get you ?
- Hi. I'll take--
- Want me to stop asking you out ?
Sorry. This will
just take a sec.
Because, Lola,
give me the word and I'll stop.
Yes, I'm gonna give you the word
because I'm an actress.
Or at least I'm trying to be one.
I'm trying to concentrate on that.
So, you know, it would be
a good thing, if you wouldn't mind,
to stop asking me out !
Honey, you seem
so stressed.
I am stressed.
I have a lot on my plate.
So, let's not talk
about this now.
Why don't I meet you here,
say, tomorrow ? 1 0:00 ? 1 0:30 ?
- Okay, that would be good.
- So, that's a date ?
It's a date.
Thank you.
Sir,
that was inspiring.
I know.
[Woman]
Good morning, Sloane-Curtis.
- Good morning, Mr. Marshall.
- Hi, honey.
- What's the dirt ?
- I was at breakfast this morning--
- Hey, Norm ! You winning ?
- Of course.
I heard Miller's shopping around,
looking for a new agency.
Miller Lite. I know.
I'm all over it.
Also, I heard Darcy McGuire left
B.B.D. and O. Good morning, Angela.
-You're kidding. Left or was fired ?
-I don't know.
Everyone there
is thrilled to get rid of her.
Well, so much for
edgy female vision.
So, that girl we met
last night at the club,
nothing happened after
you put her in the cab, right ?
It did ?
Something happened ?
But she said she had to
be in bed early.
I had her in bed by 11:00.
Or was it quarter to ?
You - You're like a genius,
you know that ?
What can I tell you, buddy ? I'm
blessed. And today is my lucky day.
Not only is my ex-wife remarrying--
right now, as a matter of fact--
but Wanamaker called me himself,
wanted to see me first thing.
- Called twice to confirm.
- Call me when he makes it official.
It's not gonna be as easy to suck up
to ''creative director,'' you know.
Not to worry. I'll make us a lunch
rez at the Drake to celebrate.
Don't count your chickens,
huh ? 1:00 ?
Pick you up.
Can I borrow this ?
- Hey, Dina.
- Hi.
Do you know the difference
between a wife and a job ?
- What is it ?
- After ten years, job still sucks.
- [ Laughing ]
- That's a good one, huh ?
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
That's not a good idea, no.
- Oh, Mr. Marshall, hi.
- Hey.
I put the storyboards on your desk.
Picked up your shoes from Barney's.
Got your glasses fixed.
There was no charge.
This morning's staff meeting
was cancelled.
And I got your cigarettes.
They're next to your laptop.
This morning's staff meeting
was cancelled.
- That's what I was told.
- Hmm.
Good morning, girls.
[ Chuckling ]
Good afternoon, sire.
Hey, anybody know why
the staff meeting was cancelled ?
Nobody called us.
Oh, but Mr. Wanamaker wants
to see you as soon as you get in,
which I told his office
was 15 minutes ago.
- I know.
- You couldn't show up on time ?
You know you're being promoted.
But you look very sharp, by the way.
- Thank you.
- Like a creative director.
- Very distinguished.
- [ Exhales Deeply ]
You able to handle yourselves
on the 44th floor ? Be truthful.
Are you kidding ?
We were made for the 44th floor.
Now, get up there already,
so we can break out the bubbly.
- Don't wait up.
- [ Both ] Don't wait up.
- He's so adorable.
- He says the cutest things.
Boy.
Sorry, buddy. I was in the board
meeting that would never end.
- Have you been here long ?
- A couple minutes. That's all.
Jess, can I get a cup of decaf
and a couple Tylenol?
And see if we got any Echinacea.
And I need some club soda.
I got something on my tie.
Know what ?Just get me another tie.
I saw the mock-ups you did for
Johnny Walker. They're fantastic.
Oh, that's my job, Dan.
So, you know l'm not great
at making speeches,
especially when I haven't
got you to write them for me.
So, I'll do my best. I've been
in this racket over 30 years.
Let me tell you something,
it doesn't get any easier.
As a matter of fact,
it gets harder and harder.
The '80s
were our glory days.
They were all about
alcohol, tobacco and cars.
I felt like
I was on top of my game.
And then in the '90s, men stopped
dominating how dollars were spent,
and we lost our compass.
Women between 16 and 24 are
the fastest-growing consumer group.
Girls who were born in the mid-'80s
control our advertising dollars.
Sorry. No Echinacea.
Hi, Nick.
- Hey.
- Red or lavender?
Red. No, no, lavender.
That'sgood.
Lavender's good. While we've been
shooting beer commercials...
with the Swedish bikini team,
the industry has been transformed.
We were the agency in town
ten years ago.
Now we're struggling
to be third.
lf we don't evolve and think
beyond our naturalability,
we're gonna go down.
''Think beyond our natural -''
I'm not quite clear what you mean.
What do you know
about Darcy McGuire ?
Oh, hey, l heard on the whisper
she just left B.B.D. and O.
I never met the woman, but
I hear she's a real man-eater.
She won that Cleo last year we
should have won for the add about--
Oh, yeah, right.
That was her ? I forgot about that.
Yeah, I wish I had. Oh, boy, I hear
she is a bitch on wheels.
- That's very funny.
- Yeah, why ?
[ Stammers ]
'Cause I just hired her.
To do what ?
You know I love you, Nick,
but it's a woman's world out there.
Getting into a women's psyche
is not exactly your strong suit.
You can get into their pants
better than anybody on Earth,
but their psyche
is a whole other ball game.
You hired Darcy McGuire
to do what ?
She hasn't done it on her own yet,
but somebody was gonna grab her.
And she's smart, Nick.
She's very smart.
You made her creative director,
didn't you ?
Sorry. This isn't easy, but I got
the board breathing down my neck.
She's coming in this afternoon.
You'll meet her.
- Come on. Roll with this.
- [ Coughs ]
Work with her because she's got what
I need to keep this place afloat.
She's got what you need,
meaning she's a woman.
You know how we can
compete with that ?
He's coming. He's coming.
He's coming.
[ Women Scream ]
Not so fast, girls.
Put it on ice.
We'll break it out soon.
We're not moving
to the 44th floor ?
Not today.
- Oh.
- Okay, Gigi, one more.
Gigi, your ex is here.
Honey, you look like...
$48 million.
Thank you.
- May I kiss the bride ?
- Sure.
- Nick.
- Nick ! Ted.
Congratulations, Ted.
You're a lucky man.
Well, thanks.
I happen to agree.
So, you're going on a cruise.
Two weeks, huh ?
Well, actually, the cruise
is just the last week.
Alexandra has an itinerary,
and I faxed one...
to your office yesterday,
to your apartment last week.
Ted's office has one,
as does the school.
-In case I've fallen off the planet?
-You never know.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, here she is. Pretty in pink.
So, two whole weeks together?
- Yeah, how you gonna handle it ?
- l'm gonna love it.
You can take care of your old man.
Cook for me. Get my slippers.
- Yeah, that'll be happening.
- Alexandra has a boyfriend now.
- Mom !
- So he won't be surprised.
You have a boyfriend ?
You're only 13 years old.
Am I ?
I thought I was 15.
[ Chuckles ]
We're gonna be fiine.
Look, I wanna meet Cameron.
- Okay if I meet Dad at his place ?
- Is it all right ?
- Yeah, well, I -
- What time ?
8:00. 9:00, maybe ?
- 7:30.
- Okay.
- Bye, Mom.
- Oh, honey. I'm gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you too.
Ted, have a good time.
- Bye, pumpkin.
- Bye.
- Nick.
- Honey.
Later.
Yeah, 7:30's fine.
Thanks for asking.
And the name's Dad.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
-Hey, I heard. I can't believe this.
-My next headache.
Don't worry.
We'll get through it.
Yeah.
[ Laughing ] Everyone, everyone,
meet Darcy McGuire.
- Oh, jeez.
- [ Applause ]
- My goodness. Everybody showed up.
- Darcy, how are you ?
- Nice to see you. Hi !
- Pleasant surprise.
- God, what a small world.
- Welcome aboard.
I'm so glad to meet you.
Hello. I'm Darcy.
Hi. I'm Nick Marshall.
Oh, I've heard
a lot about you, Nick.
-I've heard a lot about you too.
-Don't worry, can't all be true.
[ Chuckling ]
Let's hope not.
Hey.
Hey, standing room only.
It's a first.
I'm very, very excited for you all
to meet Darcy McGuire.
-[Applause]
-Darcy's extraordinary reputation...
as a leader in the field
precedes her.
At B.B.D. and O., Darcy led
a creative team...
that snagged $500 million
in new business wins.
And that was
just last year alone.
At Sloane-Curtis, we've prided
ourselves on our strategic thinking.
Now it's time for us to step up
and prove ourselves creatively...
in the marketplace.
And l'm thrilled that Darcy
has consented to move across town,
join our team and lead us
into the 21st century.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [Applause]
Thank you, Dan.
And thank you all
for that warm welcome.
Let me start off by saying
the feeling is mutual.
I am absolutely
thrilled to be here.
When I first started
in this business, it was my dream...
to work at Sloane-Curtis.
I even believe I applied
for a job here twice.
- Somebody call personnel.
- [ Laughter ]
But it was B.B.D. and O.
that offered me a home.
And what I learned there
was that any success I had...
was a direct result of the team
of people that I work with.
I know that two heads
are better than one.
I know that five heads
are better than two.
And I know that if we put our heads
and our hearts into this company,
we will deliver,
I know that.
Now, I love challenges.
I love hard work.
I look forward to sitting at this
very table tossing ideas around...
until what I fear will be
the wee hours of the morning.
I want the work we do
to say something about who we are.
- How we think, what we feel.
- I'm sorry.
[ Coughs ]
Excuse me.
So, as our friends in Hollywood say,
''Let's cut to the chase.''
How are we gonna turn
this company around ?
When Sears decided to go
after women in their advertising...
and said, ''Come see
the softer side of Sears,''
their revenues
went up 30%.
Thirty percent.
That's huge.
Female-driven advertising
totalled $40 billion last year.
And Sloane-Curtis' share
of that was ?
Zero.
If you want to sell
an anti-wrinkle cream...
or a Ford Mustang
to a woman - forgive me-
but this is the last place
you bring your business.
And we can't afford to not have
a piece of a $40 billion pie.
So, I have put together
a little kit for everybody.
Nobody panic.
This is supposed to be fun.
Every product in this box
is looking for new representation...
right now, and they're
all made for women.
l'm pretty sure all the women here
are familiar with these products,
so for the men let's just
briefly run through them.
- [ Cracking Knuckles ]
- Here you go, Nick.
Thank you.
Each kit contains
anti-wrinkle cream,
mascara,
moisturizing lipstick,
bath beads,
quick-dry nailpolish,
an at-home waxing kit,
a more wonderful Wonderbra,
- a pregnancy test, hair volumizer,
- Oh, sorry.
pore cleansing strips,
Advil,
control-top pantyhose
and a Visa card.
Now I want everybody
to come up with something--
for one product, for two,
the whole box-- whatever moves you.
We'll get together tomorrow,
have a little show-and-tell.
How's 8:30 for everybody ?
Great. See you at 8.:30
tomorrow morning.
A nightmare.
Read my lips -
night-mare.
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- Miss, miss, miss !
That's another 500 bucks.
- [Switching Channels]
- We play our dangerous game.
A game of chess...
against our old adversary.
''Adversary'' ?
Surely you mean adversary, old boy ?
Vinaigrette
for arugula salad.
- ...women's political caucus.
- Tuck the pelvis under. Lifting.
[ Impersonating Sean Connery ]
Buns of steel.
I'd steal her buns
if I could.
Here it comes.
Yes, he nailed the dismount !
Now let's check in
on the women's finals.
[ Grumbles ]
Women's finals.
There's way too much estrogen
on television these days.
And as we all know,
the perfect antidote for estrogen...
[ Grunts ]
is Frank.
Oh, I need some Frank.
Help me, buddy.
Help me now.
[ Frank Sinatra ]
[ Singing Along ]
- Don't panic.
This is supposed to be fun.
- Okay. Okay, I can do this.
I'm a professional.
Lipstick. All right.
Lipstick on a guy's collar ?
No, no, women will hate that.
Lipstick on a guy's collar
that won't rub off.
No, that's even worse.
Okay, okay, okay,
I gotta think like a broad.
All right, I'm a broad.
I see lipstick...
[ Sniffs ]
on a dark-haired
Tahitian beauty,
standing under a waterfall,
wearing nothing but a thong.
Water cascading
down her back.
I'm a lesbian.
[ Scoffs ]
I gotta change the music.
I wonder. I wonder.
Oh, Alex, thank you.
Ah, jackpot !
Oh, she's hot.
- You go, girl.
[ Singing Along ]
- Looks like big dandruff.
Smooth, yeah, smooth.
Oh, cool.
Wow, mascara.
Here we go.
[ Mumbles ]
[ Sighs ]
Nice, thick lashes.
Ow ! Ow ! Shit, that stings !
What the fu--
Okay, fine. Well, I need
some anesthetic here.
[ Exhales Deeply ]
[ Gargles ]
[ Burps ]
Beautiful.
[ Sighs ]
Okay. Now...
for the piece de resistance,
we have--
We have the right leg.
Yes, excellent.
And the hot, hot wax.
Very hot wax.
Here we go.
[ Gasping ]
Jeez ! Ooh, that's hot.
Okay, test of manhood.
Here we go.
Okay, we passed.
And next... we immediately apply
disposable cloth...
over the waxed... area.
Straight ahead.
Yes.
Yeah... it feels
kinda nice, yeah.
I don't know why women complain
about waxing their legs.
''In one smooth motion,
yank the strip quickly...
in the opposite direction
of the hair growth.''
No, no,
that would be north.
One, two, three.
[ Screams ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Scoffiing ]
[Light Clangs]
Women are insane.
Who would do that more than once ?
I don't know. Why would
anybody even do the other leg ?
Ah, yes,
that's right, girls.
Wax it off
and cover it up.
Yeah. Ally-oop !
Ooh, wait.
Oh, shit !
I guess this takes a little finesse.
One down, two to go.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Grunting ]
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
[ Clears Throat ]
Oh.
Honey, you just lost
yourself five pounds.
[ Chuckles ]
All right, where's my Wonderbra ?
Oh.
- [ Gasps ]
- Let's see which end is up here.
- Hi !
- What are you doing ?
Exfoliating ?
- Yo.
- You must be, um--
Cameron, my boyfriend.
This is Nick.
- Her father.
- That's nice nail polish you got.
Yeah, I'm just doing a new
research thing at work, you know.
- Get into the female psyche--
- Whatever.
Yeah.
I should probably
take off.
- No, you don't have to.
- It's cool. I'll see you later.
- Bye.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Nice meeting you, eh ?
Yeah.
- Excuse me. Did you kiss that guy ?
- Where did you get this ?
- Your zipper thing. You're kissing?
- You went through my stuff !
I needed some music.
It was just sitting there.
What are you, allergic to listening?
You never listen when I talk.
If I'm stuck staying here, then
my stuff's gonna be around, okay ?
I don't want you to just
go through everything.
- I don't listen to you ?
- You think you listen to me.
- Yeah.
- You do ?
What's my boyfriend's name ?
Uh, it's--
- Good night.
- No, no, wait, come back.
Dustin is his name.
Dustin, that's his name.
Right ? No.
Don't slam the--
C-Carson.
Carmen. Carmine !
Carmine !
- [DoorLocks]
- Carmichael !
I can't remember a guy's name, they
figure you're not listening to them.
[ Sighs ]
What do women want ?
I know it has three syllables.
[ Hair Dryer Whirs ]
Cameron.
His name is Cameron !
Whoa !
[ Panting ]
Oh, Jesus.
That's so dangerous.
Ninety percent
of all accidents happen--
[Sirens Wailing]
Oh, what the hell
has he done now ?
I hope he's not dead.
[ Groans ]
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine, I think.
Are you sure ?
[ Shudders ]
No. Yes.
[ Groaning ]
Cleaner pores.
Thicker hair.
Very weird headache.
Really weird.
Now I gotta clean up bras
and home pregnancy tests ?
The man doesn't pay me enough
for the things I have to do.
Oh, Jesus,
he's wearing panty hose ?
Now he's a cross-dresser ?
I was just experimenting with a few
products from work, all right ?
- Did I say anything ?
- Oh, God, it's 8:00 already.
To sleep till 8:00. He'd fire
my ass if I wasn't here to wake him.
Whew, are we
in a mood today.
Same as every other day.
Honey, make me a little bagel
with cream cheese.
You know I can't think
on an empty stomach.
For your information,
I'm not even hungry.
Who said you were ?
- Mr. Marshall.
- Good morning, Flo.
Let me get you
a cab, sir.
Sure.
- [ Whistles ]
- Thank you, Flo.
[ Thinking ]
You're welcome, my little sweet ass.
What did you say ?
Me ? Nothing.
- You sure ?
- Yes, sir.
[ Growls To Herself]
You know what ?
I think I'll walk today.
- I could use a little fresh air.
- Have a great day, sir...
with your fine ass
looking like Shaft !
Whew ! I could just
ride that puppy !
- [ Horn Honking ]
- [Man] Watch where you're going.
- You okay, sir ?
- Fine. I'm fine.
Did I turn the coffee maker off?l
walked over, but did I turn it off?
l can't remember. I saw the light,
but did I turn the switch off?
-What ? What ?
-One kiss doesn't make me a lesbian.
- Does it ?
- What ?
- Hmm ?
- Oh, sorry.
Two slices of toast, 150 calories,
plusa tab and a half of butter,
Estrogen is good for the heart
but bad for the breasts.
- What ?
- My kid doesn't need Ritalin.
- Get him to listen to what I say.
- Monsieur, I need to poop.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, boy !
[ All Thinking At Once ]
- [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- Aah !
[ Screams ]
Oh, God,
he nearly killed me.
Too bad he missed.
- [ Beeping ]
- [ Door Buzzes ]
- Good morning.
- Good mor--
Don't look up. He'll make me
hear another disgusting joke.
He's such a schmuck.
She thinks I'm a schmuck ?
Whoa, lighten up
on that aftershave, buddy.
Oh, what ? Oh, yeah,
like you've got the perfect body ?
Jeez.
- Hi, Mr. Marshall.
- No, no, don't say it.
What ? I was going to tell you
the Gillette budget's on your desk.
And I went out last night and
got you that Merlot that you wanted.
Here's
your credit card back.
Thankyou.
- You okay ?
- Me ? Yeah.
Do you realize that I have
an lvy League education...
and that running your stupid
errands has put me into therapy ?
Take me seriously and give me
some real work to do.
Oh, yeah, I remember why.
Because I have a vagina !
- Aah !
- Anything else I can get for you ?
Oh, good, you're on time.
- Morning.
- You look a little different.
You know, I think
maybe it's his hair.
- It looks thicker, doesn't it ?
- Gimme your coat.
- Oh, oh, okay.
- Mmm, you smell good today.
- New cologne ?
- No.
Th-That's it ?
No other thoughts ?
- What do you mean ?
- You feeling all right, doll ?
[ Mumbling ]
''Linens, linings,
loans, locks.''
- [Mumbling]
- Hello, Nick ?
Uh, Nick ?
We gotta go.
What are you doing ?
It's 8:30.
Can't go. Gotta find a doctor.
Need a cure. Can't go.
- Definitely can't go.
- You sound like the guy from Shine.
- What's wrong with you ?
- I don't need a doctor.
Maybe I need,
like, an exorcist.
Under ''E'' for exorcist.
There are no exorcists
in the greater Chicago area.
Let's pull it together and sell
some sensitive feminine shit, okay ?
Sorry to interrupt.
Here you go.
[ Panting ]
By the way, your hair looks
really good today, Mr. Marshall.
[ Thinking ] And it's okay
you pay me minimum wage...
because I use the company phone
to call my boyfriend in Israel...
for an hour.
Tell me you heard that.
Your hair looks really good.
So what ?
The - The other thing !
What she was thinking thing.
I don't think she thinks too much.
She's not exactly a genius.
I'll have you know she went
to an Ivy League school.
- Doubt that.
- The thing about the boyfriend,
calling him in Israel,
you heard that, yes, no ?
I didn't hear it
'cause she didn't say it.
Pull it together. We're gonna
be late for our sorority meeting.
Morgan, in case I, like,
maybe die today--
Can we walk ? 'Cause in case
you live, I don't wanna be late.
Here's what happened,
just in case the coroner asks.
I got drunk, and I tried on
all the products from the pink box.
- You did not.
- I put on all the products--
nail polish, panty hose,
everything.
- You tried on the panty hose ?
- Yes, okay.
Anyway, I was drying my hair,
and I fell over and tripped,
fell into the bathtub
and electrocuted myself.
I blacked out,
and when I woke up...
I could hear what every woman
around me was... thinking.
- Uh-huh.
- Talking personal, private stuff.
The stuff that nobody is
supposed to hear, I hear that stuff.
You know what I'm saying ?
I can hear what women think.
Can you ? Good, 'cause that's not
a talent guys have these days.
You don't believe me.
You want me to prove it ?
-See this attorney coming toward us?
-Yeah.
Oh, she thinks
you're overpaid and gay.
- What ?
- I hear what they're all thinking.
It's driving me crazy. Even
French poodles, I can hear them.
So we're on the same page,
I need you to know you sound insane.
You freaked out over losing
the job, which I understand.
But if you tell anybody you can hear
the thoughts of a French poodle--
What if I jumped out the window?
Jumped through the plate glass.
Would they notice ? Probably not
if I didn't get glass on anybody.
That girl with the fruit is funny.
Suicidal, but she is funny.
Nick, what girl
with the fruit ?
- The--
- Huh ?
Last one to arrive.
Wants me to know I'm not his boss.
Okay, you're a star.
I get the message.
She thinks I'm late because I want
her to know she's not my boss.
- What is she talking about ?
- Put a lid on it. I'm begging you.
Ooh, I can't believe
I have butterflies in my stomach.
Feels like
the first day of school.
Okay, so let's see
how we did.
[Thinking]
Nobody wants to go first.
Everyone's avoiding me,
except Nick Marshall.
Unbelievable. The only one
with good eye contact.
At least he's looking at my eyes
and not down my blouse.
- Nick, what did you come up with ?
- Me ?
What did I come up with ?
[ Chuckles ]
He's so wired.
Mostly...
[ Clears Throat ]
I thought about
the moisturizing lipstick,
never having worn
lipstick myself.
I tried to imagine what I'd want
from a lipstick, if I were a woman.
- Oh, spare me.
- Okay, he's trying to be honest.
You know,
to be perfectly honest,
I thought of a Tahitian beauty,
bathing under a waterfall.
Oy, I'm gonna die here
with these kinds of ideas.
But, uh, you know, I'm
working on it, and it's evolving.
Anybody interested in an idea
involving the Swedish bikini team ?
I do know them all
personally.
- Oh, what an idiot.
-Jerk, grow up already.
- What a pig.
- You are so foul.
I should have asked
for more money. Gina ?
I spent the night trying to figure
out how to sell Advil just to women.
You know what ?
You should sell it to women like me.
[Giggles]
I take it every time
I need to fake a headache.
Works like a charm.
I-I got a great one.
It just came to me.
- Do you mind if I interrupt, Dina ?
- Sure, go ahead.
I hate that
you've seen me naked.
[ Chuckles ]
All right.
So, we're in a bedroom,
the lights are out.
There's a woman in bed,
and she's taking an Advil.
Her husband suggestively
rubs her back, and we say, ''Advil.
''So mild and gentle,
you can take it...
even when you're
faking a headache.''
[ Laughter ]
Woman turns to her husband and says,
''Not tonight, I need an Advil. ''
- He's back.
- [ Laughs ]
What ? Come on. That doesn't
reach women on a personal level ?
- No.
- Women do that, don't they ?
- I don't.
- No ?
Sue Cranston, you've done that,
haven't you ? Faked a headache to--
No, Nick, I haven't.
Thanks for asking.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Be honest now.
I mean, you've been married
what, ten, twelve years ?
You've never faked a headache ?
lt doesn't work like a charm ?
No, Nick, I haven't.
I mean, no, it doesn't,
okay ? Jeez.
- [ Thinking ] What an asshole !
- I guess I'm off base here.
What's good is you're looking at
Advil from a woman's point of view.
Um, I don't think Advil
will go for it,
and I'm pretty sure every woman
in America will hate it.
Other than that,
I thought it was great.
You're on the right track.
Hang in there. Go ahead.
Great antenna there, babe.
The poodle give you that one ?
- [ Screams ]
- What are you doing home early ?
- I have my first migraine.
This is hideous. My boyfriend
feeling me up in front of my father.
Don't think anything. The outlook
wasn't good for the Mudville Nine.
- The score was four to two.
- Oh, shit. Where's my bra ?
- Where is it ?
- Oh, God.
Oh, God !
Okay, look. Everybody
just needs to chill out here.
There'll be no chilling.
Just get your stuff... and move on.
Come on, man. Relax.
- How old are you ?
- I just turned 1 8.
Well, she's 1 5.
She was 10 five years ago.
You know what I'm saying,
stud ? Now get out.
Dad ! [ Thinking ] We're going
to the prom. Don't ruin it.
- You're not going with this punk.
- How did you know about prom ?
Look, I don't know.
Mom told me, all right ?
It's not gonna happen
because he's too old for you.
I know what boys want, and he's not
getting it from my daughter. Door.
Your daughter ?
Suddenly, I'm your daughter.
- How am I related to this asshole ?
- Another one.
- I want Mom.
- Look, l'm just gonna take off.
- l'm real sorry about this.
- Save it.
That's mine.
Where-- Where are you--
[ Sighs ]
Great day.
[Thunderclap]
Okay, l'm not losing
my mind.
- I'm already losing my mind.
- This will work. It's gotta work.
-This has gotta work. Shit. Perfect.
- [ Screams ]
- [Thunderclap]
[Thunderclap]
Come on !
Do your thing !
Turn me into me again !
[ Hair Dryer Whirring ]
Oh, good, I'm not dead.
[ Panting ]
Oh, please !
Please, please, please.
Tell me I got rid of it.
- [ Beeping ]
- Please be a woman. Please.
- For what city, please ?
- You couldn't do me a favor...
and think of your favorite color
or TV program, could you ?
For what city, please ?
[ Sighs ]
Flo ? Hey, Flo !
- Flo ?
- [Siren Wailing]
I can't believe this.
I need a woman.
-Try this one.
-Oh, I love this. This is fantastic.
Oh, it's my mother's birthday
next week, so I need two gift sets.
You've been a great help.
I appreciate it.
Do you have a Kleenex back there
so I can wipe that off ?
I'm sure she'll like it.
It's one ofourbestsellers.
- Do I get a free gift with this ?
- Yes, you get a travelbag.
Thank you.
[ Chuckles ]
Stop it. You've got the dress.
Treat yourself to lipstick.
- No, I have enough at home.
- You might as well get one, right ?
I have too many lipsticks. I have
piles of them. I don't need it.
- I'll buy it for you.
- lf he doesn 't answer in two rings,
- I swear to God !
- Hi, blue eyes.
[ Women Thinking
Simultaneously ]
[ Nick Screaming ]
[ Buzzing ]
- Dr., you may not remember me.
- Yes ?
I'm Nick Marshall. I came here about
ten years ago with my ex-wife, Gigi.
- [ Thinking ] Oh, Christ, not him.
- Oh, good, you remember me.
I'm sorry to barge in like this,
but I don't know who to turn to.
I'm afraid to go to work.
I'm afraid of my door woman.
I'm-- I'm afraid
to get a cup of coffee.
Mr. Marshall,
please slow down. Slow down.
Let me make sure I completely
understand what it is you're saying.
[ Sighs ]
All right. All right.
I hear what women think.
Yeah. You know,
Mr. Marshall,
this kind of imaginary
displacement scenario...
- I'm not imag--
- really isn't my thing.
I do, however, have a very good
friend over at University Hospital,
who specializes in male menopause
and testosterone depletion.
She's fabulous. I think what I'll do
is just give her a ring...
and send you overthere.
Why did I answer my door ? I was so
into buying that lamp on eBay.
- How much was it going for ?
- How much was what going for ?
The lamp on eBay.
Oh, I see. That's good.
Very clever.
- Dr. Skolnick, please.
- You don't believe me. Try another.
Go on. Pick a number.
Give it a whirl. Any number.
Okay. A number
between one and--
- A million. Why not ?
- One and a million.
All right.
Mm.
644,998-- 99-- 90.
Wanna make a decision here ?
- Oy vay!
- Oh, you can say that again.
- I didn't say anything.
- Doesn't mean I didn't hear it.
Okay. Okay. Let's say--
Let's say I do believe you.
- Yeah.
- You can hear what women think.
Even though I'm a grown
woman of... [ Thinking ] 51 .
- 47.
- Oh, my lips are sealed.
Holy crap !
Oh, forgive me.
- That's all right.
- But this is phenomenal.
- You can hear inside my head.
- Yes.
Why would you want to get rid
of such a brilliant gift ?
Well, for starters,
almost every woman I know
thinks I'm an asshole.
- What I thought when I met you.
- Doc, give me a break here.
Mr. Marshall, you might
find this a little unorthodox,
but would you mind
awfully if I smoked ?
- No, no, I understand.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
[ Coughs ]
Let's try to look at
the up side of this, shall we ?
You know, Freud died at age 83
still asking one question,
''What do women want ?''
Wouldn't it be strange and wonderful
if you were the one man on Earth...
finally able to answer
that question ?
Listen to me, Nick.
Something extraordinary...
and I think miraculous
has happened to you.
My advice is
you must learn from this.
You know, there isn't
a single woman that I treat...
that doesn't wish her man
understood her better.
If men are from Mars and women are
from Venus and you speak Venusian,
the world can be yours.
I don't know how this
happened to you or why,
but you may just be
the luckiest man on Earth.
lmagine the possibilities.
lf you know
what women want,
you can rule.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Thinking ] Hubba-hubba, here he
comes, looking awfully good today.
And I haven't had sex
in four months. Okay, six.
Why did I tell him to stop
asking me out ? I'm an idiot!
- Idiot ! Idiot !
- [ Chuckling ]
Hey, Nick, how's it going ?
Lola, my love.
I can't take no for an answer.
- About what ?
[ Chuckles ]
About us.
Just don't hurt me, Nick.
I've been hurt too many times.
I know how hard it is
to go out with someone new.
I mean, there's always
that fear of,
well, getting hurt.
- At least that's how I feel inside.
- You do, really ?
- [ Sighs ] All the time.
- Me, too, all the time.
Let's just take it slow
and see how it goes.
Slow is good.
Slow is really good.
- Yeah.
- Are you free tonight ?
So, you don't think I'm gay ?
You're saying you never said that ?
- I never said that.
- Doesn't mean you didn't think it.
Is it the hair ? The highlights
happen to be natural.
- Morgan, I have a meeting.
- You don't think I'm overpaid?
- You never said that.
- I don't think I ever said that.
Okay.
[ Thinking ]
Who has he been talking to ?
- Morning.
Well, then check your E-mail.
I sent it over--
Hi, Annie.
How's the boyfriend in Israel ?
I want to thank you
for picking up that wine.
That's above and beyond.
I appreciate it so much. Thank you.
Uh, can I get you
a cup of coffee or, um,
some water
or any kind of beverage ?
No, but thank you. If I'm thirsty,
I know where the coffee room is.
That's right, guys, don't help.
Just walk right past me.
Why don't you step on
my hands, you big--
- Here you go. How you doing ?
- Oh.
Oh, fine.
Thank you, Mr. Marshall.
- You're welcome, um--
- Erin.
Erin. You be careful,
all right, Erin ?
Yeah, sure.
Heavy.
What do you know ?
There is life on this planet.
Breakfast Tuesday sounds great.
Absolutely.
Thanks for the info.
And thanks for the champagne.
You too.
Okay, bye-bye.
Set meeting, Nike,
women's division.
- Hi.
Well, you've been here five minutes.
Looks like you've been here a year.
Oh, yeah. I'm compulsive.
It's a problem.
[Thinking] Why do I always
feel like he's checking me out ?
I wonder what he's got
up his sleeve.
- Great photographs.
- No clue they're all Bourke-White.
They're not all Margaret
Bourke-White, are they ?
Yeah, they are.
Wow. It's
a beautiful collection.
- Thanks. So how's it going ?
- Mmm.
You know, I was gonna
ask you the same thing.
It's starting slow.
- I'm evaluating staff, that's hard.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, right.
Well, you know, I don't
wanna beat around the bush.
- What I'd like to propose--
- He's proposing so soon ?
- Oh, sorry. Sorry. [ Chuckles ]
- Oh !
- Uh, yes--
- Excuse me.
- You got another one. Wow !
- [Darcy] Thanks.
[ Chuckling ]
As I was saying,
I know nothing about the products
you're going for personally,
but I do believe
I can sell anything...
once I know
what the buyer's needs are.
And what I'd really like,
with your kind indulgence of course,
is to go after
that really big fish.
I mean, the one
you really wanna land.
I'll learn what I need to know,
and I'll reel them in for us.
No, actually, I think
l'll reel them in for us.
That is, unless you're going after
something in particular yourself.
No. It's just that there're several
big fish out there at the moment.
Oh, yeah ?
Well, what's your biggest fish ?
To your mind,
who's your whale ?
Um, Nike--
women's division ?
You heard
they were shopping ?
I got wind of it.
- Amazing. I heard no one knew.
- You knew.
- I heard no one else knew.
- It's okay if I know what you know.
- We're on the same team. Besides,
- Yeah.
I heard someone say once
two heads are better than one--
- Oh, you were listening.
- More than you know.
Okay,
here's what I heard.
Nike is shopping,
quietly.
But if they make a change,
it's gonna happen fast.
Now, you know this is
a tough one for us to get.
It would be a tough one for anybody
to get, but if we got it--
- That's all we'd need.
- I hear you.
So, what do they want
exactly ?
They wanna empower women.
- What ?
- I'm sorry.
- That won't work.
- No, okay. I'm sorry.
- I understand. Go on.
- They wanna get in women's heads...
and reach them
on a very real level.
Don't take this wrong, but you got
jumpy talking about lipstick.
- I know.
- Nike is hard-core woman power.
You sure you wanna
go after this one ?
You get 'em here in two weeks,
I'll be ready.
[ Chuckles ]
This guy is kind of exciting.
Hey !
Glad I caught you both.
- You got a minute ?
- Sure.
I want you to look at these boards
for U.S. Air before they come by.
- Right.
- lt feels like something's missing.
Hmm. I don't like
the graphics.
Feels a bit parochial.
Maybe it should be
in black and white.
- What do you think, Nick ?
- I don't know who you've had,
but, I don't know,
it seems kind of--
What's the word ?
Parochial to me.
Um, what do you think,
Darcy ?
I totally agree,
especially about the graphics.
They're parochial.
It's so funny you just said that.
Yeah ?
Why don't you get them to
try it in black and white ?
Might punch it up
a little.
What ?
Did you say something ?
No. I just swear I was
thinking the exact same thing.
[ Weak Chuckle ]
Were you ?
Black and white could really help.
Good idea, Nick.
Good idea, Nick ?
Speak up. Quick.
- Say something before he leaves.
- Uh, Dan ?
Want me to look at the boards ? Once
they have a stab, give me a buzz.
- I will. Thanks, buddy.
- Dan ?
ln case they find Nick's idea
too retro, which they might--
-Oh, yeah.
-they may think it's old-fashioned--
I'd be ready with some--
maybe a dot com kind of thing ?
Maybe there's something about
getting on-line at the airport.
No, I think we're fine, really.
Really, we're good.
- I like Nick's fix on this.
- Great.
Hey, you wanna come by later ? I got
a box of new Cubans, just came in.
- Great.
- Cool.
You smoke cigars ?
No.
You know, your office
is looking really snazzy.
- I love the red.
- Thanks.
Mr. Marshall,
your daughter's on line one.
- Oh. I'm sorry. Would you mind--
- Oh. Here you go.
He has a daughter ?
Didn't picture that. How old ?
She's 15. She's staying with me
while her mom's away.
- He's married ?
- Away on her honeymoon.
- Oh.
- Alex, hi.
Uh-huh. Oh, sure, honey.
No, that's great.
''Honey'' ?
Who are you trying to impress ?
Okay, look, I'm gonna go out
with my friends after school.
Then can I bring them back to your
place, or will you freak out again ?
No, no, no, no.
No problem. Whatever you want.
- What time are you gonna be home ?
- Wait for me !
- I don't know. I gotta go.
- 8:00's fine.
l love you too.
Bye, sweetie.
Total shocker.
He's like a nice guy.
- Sorry, duty calls.
- Oh, of course.
- She's 15 ?
- Yeah. Got a boyfriend that's 1 8.
- And you hate that, right ?
- [ Groans ] Hate it.
Yeah. But she digs him,
and he's invited her to the prom.
- That's a big deal, I guess.
- The prom is about the dress.
- You know that, right ? Oh, yeah.
- Is it ?
Once you got the dress handled,
it's all downhill from there.
This feels like a date. Why did I
go into all that ? He needs to go.
Well, I'm out of here.
Do some research downtown,
get inside women's heads.
- Well, if you need any help--
- I'll be picking your brain.
- You got it.
- I'll take it.
Oh, God.
Candy.
She won't last a month.
Oh, I like that one, but it says
you can't wear it if you have hips.
-That one's cute.
-It's low-cut. I can't wear low-cut.
- [Nick Knocking At Door]Alex ?
- It's open.
What? Say something.
Uh, hi.
I'm Alex's dad, Nick.
- Hi.
- Deadbeat.
- Mr. No-Food-in-the-House.
[Girl
Forgot her birthday.
Why is he just standing there ?
Oh, I-I just wanted
to let you know that I was home...
and that I got sort of a date
later on tonight, so I'm going out.
But I'll be home early. Hey,
why don't you guys order a pizza ?
There's not a scrap of food
in the joint.
I also wanted to know if maybe you
and I could go out on a date soon ?
I'd like to take you shopping
for a prom dress.
Oh, that is so sweet.
I wish my dad would do
something like that.
- [Girl
- [Alex] I don't get it.
First, you throw Cameron out.
Now you wanna take me shopping
so I can go to the prom with him ?
I overreacted, and I just wanna make
up for it by taking you shopping.
I mean, it's a pretty
important thing, you know ?
They say it's all downhill
after the dress.
He must be stoned.
Fine.
I'll get the most expensive dress,
shoes, makeup. He can afford it.
And what the hell.
Let's go crazy.
While we're at it, we'll get you
new makeup, shoes, the works.
- What do you say ?
- Fine, whatever.
Whatever meaning ''yes.''
Yes ?
Yes.
Great. Nice to have met you two.
I hope to see you again soon.
- Definitely.
- Bye, Mr. Marshall.
- Love the apartment.
- Great view.
Thank you.
Oh, okay.
I gotta tell ya, I'm not
usually like this on a first date.
It's just... you've been
so amazing all night.
- You've been so sensitive...
- Oh, well--
and so understanding and--
Hey.
- You wanna come up ?
- Oh, yeah.
I can't believe I asked him up.
Am I ready for him to come up ?
If I sleep with him, he'll think
I'm a slut and never call me again.
Or he'll call me all the time 'cause
he'll think he can get it whenever.
Oh, what's the difference ?
He's so incredible !
He reminds me of my sister.
- So, what do you think ?
- Well, I--
I'll only come up
if you really want me to.
I don't want you to do anything
you're not ready for.
- I can wait.
- [ Squeals ]
- Oh, he's got a great body.
But-- Whoa !
What's with the tongue ? I'm
gonna need the Heimlich maneuver.
Thank you.
Ooh.
- Ouch ! Right, they're attached.
- I'm sorry.
Oh !
Now we're talkin'.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
Okay.
Lied about the grande.
[ Groans ]
Would you mind if we had
the lights on, maybe ?
- No, you want the light on ?
- Yeah, it might help.
Okay, if it'll help.
God, I hope he's better
with the light on.
He's so all over the place.
Just do it so I can start faking it.
Is Britney Spears
on Leno tonight ?
[ Panting ]
- You okay ?
- Well--
Yeah, I'm just fine.
What--
What happened ?
Shaking--
[ Groans ]
Okay. All right.
Now, let's pull this
together, buddy.
I mean,
this is what we do.
- You okay ?
- Yeah.
Just regrouping.
- [ Chuckling ]
- Lola ?
- I can do this better.
- Wanna bet ?
Yeah.
[Train Passing By]
[Moaning]
Amazing !
Amazing.
Oh ! It was like...
you were more inside of me
than anybody ever !
- [ Panting ]
- Well, thanks, doll.
- I tried.
- No, no.
- I mean, more inside my head.
- Oh.
Like, you knew what I wanted
and how I wanted it.
We connected in a way
that was beyond--
beyond--
Oh, my heart !
My heart is beating
so hard.
[ Thinking ]
Who would've thought ? Slow starter,
then turns out to be
a genius in bed.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Nick Marshall is a sex god !
Oh, yeah.
- [ Women's Voices Thinking ]
- [ Voices Overlapping ]
- [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- Living life.
- Life. Livin' it.
- Ooh. That's good.
- [ Bell Dings ]
- [ Thinking, Indistinct ]
Ha !
I love it.
- [KnockingAt Door]
- [Dan] I know. I know.
- Wait a minute.
- No, it's great.
[ All Laughing ]
Okay, that was a--
One more. Time for one more.
Okay, you know why guys like
doing it in front of the mirror ?
- Why ?
- Objects may appear larger.
- That's a good one. Anyway.
- Oh, that's a good one.
I heard that in
the beauty shop this morning.
- But seriously. Dee ?
- Huh ?
That other thing we were
talking about before.
Come on. I mean, he can't
just ignore you all night,
stay glued to the TV
like some zombie...
and then expect you
to turn it on like a lightbulb.
I mean, I wouldn't
put up with that.
I mean, you're either
interesting or you're not.
Ask him to decide.
- Can I write that down ?
- All right.
I'm either interesting
or I'm not. He'll shit a brick.
Hmm.
What if he says I'm not ?
He won't say
that you're not.
Trust me.
Okay, I did it.
I told Chaim
I wasn't moving to Israel.
Yeah, good.
And ?
I said what you said.
He can be a writer anywhere.
If I'm going to be in advertising,
I need to be here and not there.
[ Whistles ]
And then he said ?
- I don't know. It was in Hebrew.
- Ooh.
But I don't think it was,
''You got it. See you next Tuesday.''
I don't know. I'd wait it out.
He'll call you.
I can't.
I better call him back.
Be strong.
He will call you.
Well, girls, been nice chattin'.
I gotta get back to work.
[ All Chattering ]
- Can I make you a sandwich ?
- No, l'm cool.
Really.
But thank you, anyway.
This was fun.
[ All ]
Aww !
[ Thinking ]
Huh. This is good.
More insightful
than I would've thought.
This line doesn't feel
exactly right.
If you're thinking that line isn't
perfect, I agree. It needs work.
There's something not exactly
right about it, isn't there ?
I mean, it's not bad. It's
insightful, actually. It's just--
Well, what do you think
this woman's thinking ?
Uh, well, I--
Let's see.
Uh, she's thinking about
what she wants out of life.
What's she gonna accomplish ?
How's she gonna do all that ?
Women, you know,
they think about that a lot.
I mean,
surprisingly a lot.
They worry all the time
about everything.
You're so right.
How do you know that ?
Well, you know,
even I had a mother.
[ Chuckles ]
Well--
So maybe running gives her
time off from all of that.
It gives her something she can't
get anyplace else. Look at her.
God.
I want to be her.
She looks so free,
doesn't she ?
No one's judging her,
no boss to worry about,
no guys to worry about,
no games to figure her way through.
I like that.
No games. That's good.
That'd be nice in life,
wouldn't it ?
Okay, can I just think
for one second ?
- Take your time.
- Okay.
Okay.
No games.
How do I get that in ?
She's running.
lt's early, it's quiet.
Just the sound of her feet
on the asphalt.
She likes to run alone.
No pressure, no stress.
This is the one place
she can be herself.
Look any way she wants,
dress, think any way she wants.
No gameplaying, no rules.
Games, sports, rules.
Playing by the rules.
Playing games versus playing--
- Why are you nodding ?
- Because you're onto something.
- Am I ?
- Aren't you ?
Well, I was thinking about
a play on words.
Something about games versus--
I feel like
I was onto something good.
- Playing games versus playing--
- Sports ?
Yes ! Thank you.
Do you like any of this ?
A lot. I like the idea that you can
be yourself on the road.
I do too.
Did I say that out loud ?
[ Stammering ]
No, I was just--
'Cause I was circling around
the exact same thing,
-which is great, we're on the same--
-Yeah.
Sorry, I'm not thinking straight.
My glands may be swollen.
Maybe they should be more swollen.
You're doing great. Nike. No games.
Just sports.
- Oh.
- You should write that down.
All right.
Did he come up with that,
or did I ?
Boy, can I be--
What ?
Uh, well,
can I be honest with you ?
Please do.
Before I came here, I heard you
were a tough, chauvinistic prick.
I didn't know you were
gonna be that honest.
- Sorry. I'm-- Sorry.
- No, that's all right.
No, that's okay. You must have
looked so forward to meeting me.
I was dreading it. I had this whole
other person built up in my mind.
Well, since we're sharing,
I heard a few things about you too.
Yes, I'm sure. I'm the ''man-eating
bitch Darth Vader'' of the ad world.
Verbatim.
Really ? All right.
Well, nice to meet you.
That's not who I am at all.
Just for the record,
I don't think that's who you are.
I don't.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
See, no games equals
embarrassing moment.
Don't fall for a guy at work.
- Don't fall for a guy at work.
- Why ?
Why what ?
Why won't-- Why don't I just
work on these storyboards...
and then bring them back around
to you tomorrow if you're free.
I'm free.
Just call me anytime.
l'm flirting.
What's wrong with me ?
God ! I just looked at his penis.
I hope he didn't see me.
Oh, shit ! I just looked
at it again ! Stop it !
- Are you all right ?
- Fine. I got something in my eye.
Allright, um--
So, great.
So tomorrow will be--
That'll be great. I'll see you then.
- Uh, good work by the way.
- You too.
- You sure you're all right ?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Are you laughing at me ?
- Yeah.
- Good.
I didn't think anyone else
was still here.
- I didn't know anyone was here.
- What time is it ?
It's after 1 0:00.
- I didn't realize it was so late.
- [ Thinking ] I feel so alone.
Um-- I didn't catch that.
Sorry ?
- I didn't realize how late it was.
- And I'm glad you're here.
I'm stuck.
I feel so alone.
- You want a hand with this ?
- No, thanks. I'm okay.
Yeah, I'm not buying it.
What's going on ?
Well, I have an early meeting
tomorrow with Dan,
and I wanted to make it
later so I could be more prepared.
But then you slipped in there
and took the only time he had left,
which left me with
8:15 tomorrow morning.
It's fine. I'm just not
as ready as I wish I was.
- Sorry.
- You didn't do it on purpose.
[Coughs]
I just don't want him
to be disappointed.
Hey, why don't we go through
some of these together ?
- Really ?
- I insist.
- Unless you're too tired.
- Oh, no.
- I'm not tired.
- Yeah, I can see that.
It's just so far beyond
tired at this point.
I've basically stopped sleeping
ever since I took this job.
- You have ?
- Yeah, it's weird.
I, um--
[ Thinking ] How do I say this ?
You don't feel quite
like yourself here, do you ?
No, I don't.
Not yet, anyway.
Boy.
Plus, I'm mad
that I'm getting sick.
I never, ever get sick.
In fact,
you don't have to sit
so close to me if you don't want to.
No, come here.
I'll brave it.
So, where do we kick off ?
- Control-top panty hose ?
- Okay.
Personally, I think
they do the trick.
You've worn
control-top panty hose ?
- Did you put a pair in the box ?
- Seriously ?
Oh, yeah.
- You are full of surprises.
- Yeah.
No, no, no. I mean that
as a compliment. I love that.
- And how did you look in them ?
- Ooh. Hot.
My daughter and her boyfriend
walked in, and I got 'em on with--
And they said what when
they saw you in your panty hose ?
It was the turquoise Wonderbra
they noticed. Then, the nail polish.
[ Indistinct ]
[Alex] The dress
you picked out is totally hideous.
- l'm not coming out.
- It can't be that bad. Come on out.
I look like a nun--
an ugly nun.
Why ? Because it's gray ?
Gray is the new black.
If he says he likes it,
I'll die.
Okay, next.
This, I love.
Thank you.
Next.
I think this is the one.
I like that--
No, I love that.
Okay, this is it.
Let me take a look.
Yes !
I look older.
This is great.
Oh, God, I need boobs.
Oh, I'll buy a padded bra
when he's not around.
I can't believe this is what I'll be
wearing the last night I'm a virgin.
- Or what I'll be taking off.
- [ Yells ]
- Alex ?
- Hmm ?
I wanna talk to you about something
that's pretty important.
- I've never talked to you about--
- Oh, God.
He's actually gonna try
to be a dad.
This should be hilarious.
I realize I haven't been
the perfect dad.
[ Thinking ] Understatement of the
century. Can you pass the bread ?
Yeah, sure, sure. But that does
not mean I don't have the right...
to talk to you about--
about--
- [ Clears Throat ]
- About ?
All right.
You're a young woman now,
and you may be flirting
with the idea of-of--
Having sex ?
Um, can I get a lemonade,
please ?
Well, you know, boys and girls
think very differently about sex.
My hunch is girls just want guys
to like 'em and hang out with 'em.
Whereas guys--
And not all guys, allright ?
But most guys, they pretty much
just wanna have sex.
Okay, I'm--
What I'm trying to say here is,
I don't want you
to feel pressured...
- because your boyfriend's older.
- Please. Save it.
Mom had this talk with me
when I was, like, 11.
You're supposed to have sex when
you're in love and it's special.
And Mom knows me for real
and knows my friends and Cameron,
so let's leave the parental
talks up to her, okay ?
- I promised Cameron I'd do it.
- Oh, jeez.
And also, let's not make me
part of this Nick makeover...
or whatever this new thing
you're into is, okay ?
- What new thing ?
This ridiculous new guy
you're trying to be.
Clowning around with me ?
Asking if we can make a salad ?
Watch Friends together ?
I mean, it's nuts
after 15 years of no relating.
I mean, come on.
Who are you to talk about
relationships anyway ?
You never had a real relationship
with anyone in your entire life.
Look, l'm supposed
to meet my friends.
- So I'm gonna go, okay ?
- Sure.
Thanks for the dress.
[Woman Thinking]
She didn 't even finish her lunch.
Johnny-come-lately,
giving her advice ?
- Oh, teenagers.
- I think the talk worked.
- She's totally right.
- Move on, dude. It's over.
[ Groans ]
Please.
Now you've seen how
the cake is assembled.
The next time you admire a wedding
cake, you'll be able to appreciate--
Wow.
It looks so gorgeous.
- [ Announcer ] Fit, vibrant hair.
- Oh.
I hated being overweight. I always
wanted to be thin and pretty...
and wear cute little clothes.
lt built and it built,
and my health deteriorated.
And I couldn 't walk
and I couldn 't stand...
to even stand up at the park for
ten minutes while my kids played.
I tried sitting on the swings, and
the chains cut my hips and it hurt.
And I couldn't -
I couldn 't run and I couldn 't move.
And I was tired
and I wanted to be a good mom.
[ Sobbing ]
- What the hell's wrong with me ?
- [Telephone Ringing]
- Hello ?
- [ Thinking ] What am I doing ?
- [TVShuts Off]
- Darcy ?
How did you know it was me ?
I didn't say anything.
I, uh, just sensed it.
Shit. I'm such an idiot.
I didn't think he'd be there.
- Excuse me ?
- I didn't mean to really call you.
I had your number here,
and I was thinking of you.
Thinking of calling you.
Obviously,
I did call you.
Oh, no, that's all right.
I, uh--
I was thinking about you too.
Well, here's to another
great idea.
- What, ''Let's meet for a drink'' ?
- Yes.
- Yeah ?
- Exactly what I wanted to say.
Sometimes I think
you're a bit of a mind reader.
But I don't have to be
a mind reader with you.
- Hmm.
- You always say what you think.
- I know. It's a curse.
- What--
- Are you kidding ?
It's a relief-- an enormous relief.
Do you know how rare that is
to actually say what you think ?
Do you have any idea how rare it is
for someone to actually like that ?
Trust me, this has not been
a great thing in my life.
My ex-husband didn't love me.
Let's just put it that way.
He didn't love you ?
Did I just say that ?
Oh, God !
[ Laughs ]
Um, I meant to say ''it.''
He didn't love it--
that I spoke my mind.
If you wanna know the truth,
I'm not sure he did really love me.
- Ooh.
- There's a conversation starter.
God. A smart person would
just get so very drunk now.
How long
were you married ?
A little less than a year.
I've been divorced about nine
months now. We worked together.
- You know that, right ?
- Oh, yeah. I knew that.
- I heard it.
- Hmm.
- What was that like ?
- It was great in the beginning.
But it changed.
It became competitive.
Suddenly, the better I did,
the worse we did.
The price I pay
for being me.
- I know that now. No, truly.
- [ Chuckles ]
- Oh.
- No, no, it's true.
Do you wanna know
all this about me ?
Keep going.
Well, that's why I needed
to get out there on my own,
as scary as it was.
I mean, not scary,
but, um--
Well, yeah,
I was kind of scared.
- Why ?
- I don't know.
I guess I wasn't sure
I could do the job.
I mean,
I thought I could do it,
but I'm finding Sloane-Curtis
a tougher place than I thought.
I'm sorry.
- I know you were up for my job.
- No.
- I'm sorry I'm the one that got it.
- I'm-I'm not. I'm not.
- I've learned a lot from you.
- Like what ?
Like what ? For starters,
you really love what you do.
- You really love what you do.
- Not as much as you do.
How can you say that ?
You're so great at it.
I think Dan's even wondering
why he hired me. Really.
I think the bloom
is definitely off the rose.
You wanna hear something
really great ?
Yeah.
I just closed escrow on
my first apartment ever.
Finally, I own my own place.
- What? I wish I was a mind reader.
- No.
I was just thinking...
how men like me
can get so screwed up.
I don't think
there are men like you.
If we kissed,
would it ruin everything ?
Listen to me.
I think...
you are one of
the great women.
I really do.
I'm sorry.
But I just meant to say
thank you.
I'm so sorry.
Well, I, uh,
guess I'll see you...
in, let's see,
three and a half hours.
Nick, may I just say...
you are an exceptionally
great kisser.
No, I mean
really, really great.
Well, I haven't had
this much fun making out since--
I've never had
this much fun making out.
Me either.
- Don't let this get weird at work ?
- No.
We have nothing
to be embarrassed about.
We made out.
You and I made out.
- And if I may, it was--
- Sexy as hell.
God. That's just what
I was about to say.
But I think I said it first,
I think.
- Oh, no, you did.
- Oh.
Um, well,
all right, then.
Oh, I'm a grown woman.
Just say it.
Do you want to come back
to my place ?
Say it !
Do you want to come--
Good night, Darcy.
Good night.
What am I doing ?
Lola.
It's okay. Okay.
Here he comes.
- [Lola Muttering, lndistinct]
- Lola ?
I know I haven't
heard from you.
Lola, how long
have you been out here ?
Just a few... hours.
Nick, you said that
you wouldn't hurt me.
And then you slept with me, and then
you didn't call me for six days.
So that, in the world of me,
that's torture.
I mean, we have this totally
unbelievable, life-altering sex,
and then
you just disappear.
I mean, you-you-you
stopped drinking coffee !
Lola, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay, because
I figured out your little secret.
- You did ?
- It's so obvious.
How else would you know
the things that you know ?
- It wasn't obvious to anybody else.
- Nick, come on.
You're so sensitive.
You're so aware of my feelings.
You're so tuned in.
You talk to me like a woman,
you think like a woman.
Nick ! Come on ! Admit it.
You're totally and completely gay.
- I am ?
- You're not ?
Oh ! I mean, if you're not,
you gotta tell me.
Based on the other night--
Just put me out of my misery.
Are you or aren't you ?
Say you're gay. Then l'm not nuts.
l'm not undesirable.
Not rejected by another guy !
Say it ! Say you're gay ! Admit it !
Okay.
I'm gay.
How gay ?
Oh !
I'm as gay as it gets.
You're gonna make some guy
very happy someday.
Oh, from your lips.
God, I hate that
I'm crying.
Well, look it.
If things should ever change
in that department--
- You'll be the first to know.
- You promise ?
Oh, yeah, I promise.
Come here.
Oh, boy.
-It was very nice meeting you, Nick.
-And you.
Thanks for pep talk, yes ?
You two just
take care of each other.
- And thanks for the yarmulke.
- Oh, no problem.
- You wear it well, yes ?
- Happy trails, kids.
- Isn't he great ?
- Darcy !
I need to talk to you.
Uh-oh, look at him.
I knew it. He is weird about it.
This is not about last night.
It's about the Nike meeting.
And I honestly believe
in my gut...
- that you should make the pitch.
- Oh, God.
-I guilted you into this last night.
-No, no.
- It would be better if you did it.
- No, no, no.
This is your baby.
You've gotta do it.
I gotta go meet and greet
these folks. I'll see you in there.
- It's not my baby.
- Yes, it is.
I predict no one will even know I'm
gone until the files start to build.
It could be days.
And then someone
will finally ask,
''Where's the geek in the glasses
who carries all the files ?''
Do either of you two know what
the story is on this Erin girl ?
- Miss Lonely Hearts ? Who knows ?
- Yeah.
Ooh, I know.
She's been here two years.
She tried to be a copywriter
but got turned down.
- So she got stuck as a messenger.
- What fool turned her down ?
You did, sire.
Well, did I ever
meet with her at least ?
I don't think so. As I recall,
you told me to ''blow her off.''
Well, I wanna meet
with her now.
The kid's got something.
She's kind of funny.
This is your lucky day. I just saw
the Nike group get off the elevator.
All women. Your specialty.
Come on. I'll walk you up.
I hate what I'm doing to Darcy.
I hate it !
I'm gonna write her
a long letter, confess everything.
- You're doing Darcy ? Since when ?
- No !
I said I hate what
I'm doing to Darcy.
- Men are stupider. It's true.
- Will you stop it ?
- They are.
- ''They'' ? Are you a woman now ?
Oh, I wish. A woman wouldn't have
screwed over the woman she loved.
No, they don't think that way.
And another thing.
- This thing about penis envy.
- Yeah.
Not true. No.
They don't envy it.
Half of'em
don't even like it.
You know who has
penis envy ? We do.
That's why we cheat
and screw up and lie,
because we're all obsessed
with our own equipment.
- You ready ? Okay.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
[Nick] You don't stand in front
of a mirror before a run...
and wonder what the road
will think of your outfit.
You don't have to listen to its
jokes and pretend they're funny.
lt would not be easier to run
if you dressed sexier.
The road doesn't notice
if you're not wearing lipstick.
lt does not care
how old you are.
You do not feel
uncomfortable...
because you make more money
than the road.
And you can call on the road
whenever you feel like it,
whether it's been a day...
or even a couple of hours
since your last date.
The only thing
the road cares about...
is that you pay it a visit
once in a while.
Nike.
No games.
Just sports.
- [Woman Thinking]He nailed it.
- They hit a home run.
[Woman
Where do we sign ?
[Frank Sinatra On Stereo]
[ Singing Along ]
Why are you not the happiest guy
in Chicago right now ?
You just did so great.
No, no, I didn't do so great.
We did so--
No, actually,
you did so great.
- You.
- You, me.
We did great !
Will you come with me someplace ?
I wanna show you something.
- I have something I need to finish.
- Please ?
Please.
Okay.
Here you go.
- Come with me.
- All right.
-Should I close my eyes or anything?
-No.
So, you see those top
two floors right there ?
I do.
- All mine.
- Wow.
Come here.
So this is my--
living room.
It's beautiful.
What are you thinking ?
You've got that look
you have sometimes.
Yeah ? No. I was just wondering
when you get to move in.
Well, they said
two weeks, so--
Okay.
This is the dining room.
- The fireplace works. Come here.
- Wow.
I can see elegant parties in here.
Waiters with caviar,
- you in a beautiful gown.
- You can see all that ?
Maybe you're naked and I'm the only
guest, but it'd still be elegant.
Okay.
So this is upstairs.
There's a second bedroom
or a future office or whatever.
- And this is my boudoir.
Your boudoir comes with
pretty decent music.
It does.
Where is that coming from ?
Let's turn up the volume.
So, where's your bed going ?
Uh, right... here.
So, if you had a bed,
we'd be dancing on it.
I like it here.
I like it here too.
No. I mean,
I like it here.
Oh.
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Dan] Believe me, we're
as excited as you are.
- Dan ? I gotta talk to you.
- Yeah ?
He'll be there. Bye. I gotta
talk to you too. That was Nike.
They're gonna announce to the trades
that we won the account.
I gotta hand it to you. You saved
my ass. You saved the company's ass.
Actually, Dan, I had very little
to do with saving anybody's ass.
It's Darcy you should be thanking,
that's what I want to talk about.
Darcy ? Please. I was there.
The girl didn't open her mouth.
Look, I'm a big enough man
to admit when I screw up.
I looked at the marketplace
and I panicked.
Nick, forgive me.
I want you to step in here.
No, no, no, no. Dan, you did
the right thing when you hired her.
I mean, she is the best creative
director I have ever seen, bar none.
- This isn't about-- She's adorable.
- Oh, yeah, she is.
- But this isn't about that ?
- No, no. Not like that. No, no.
Please. Look.
I've been doing
a lot of listening lately.
And I've decided...
I need to take a leave of absence.
I need to get away from here
and get some perspective on things.
What are you, nuts ? What is this ?
What do you mean ?
This is the biggest account
this company has ever landed.
Do you want me to have
nobody running the shop ?
What are you talking about ?
Darcy's here.
For somebody who listens a lot,
you don't hear so well.
I had a meeting with her today.
I sat her down.
- We had a talk.
- Oh, Dan ! You didn't.
- Tell me you didn't fire her.
- She didn't even put up a fight.
- Oh, Dan, no !
- Hey, she's gone, pal.
No, no. It's not too late.
Look, call her.
Tell her you need her back,
you made a mistake. Hire her back.
- Hey, calm down. I can't do that.
- Why ?
Because I talked to the board and I
told them I don't need her anymore.
- Oh !
- They offered her a settlement.
Besides, Nike says they want you.
You're what they bought.
- [ Groans ]
- I got a delivery-- Can I--
Would you come out for one second ?
Let me tell you something.
My job is to deliver you.
Dan, Nike bought an idea.
It wasn't even mine.
Every good idea that they loved
yesterday came from her.
And if you don't get Darcy McGuire
back in here, and I mean pronto,
the board is gonna be
paying you your settlement.
This is all about
saving your ass, right ?
Save it.
Annie, get a hold of Darcy's address
and number as quick as possible.
- Yeah, sure.
- Where's the girl in glasses ?
Erin ? I don't think
she's in today.
- Did she call in sick ?
- I don't think so. Didn't show up.
Oh, where does she live ?
-Does anyone know where Erin lives ?
-[Man] Who's Erin ?
And then someone
will finally ask,
''Where's the geek in the glasses
who carries all the files ?''
[ Whistling ]
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Hey. Yeah.
Did you get a hold of Darcy ?
No ? Keep trying. And when you get
a hold of her, tell her to stay put.
I'm coming right over. I just have
to make a little stop on the way.
Do you know where this is ?
Down the alley.
Just down the alley.
Thanks.
- Come on, Erin. Be there. Please--
- [Cat Meows]
Erin ?
Hello ?
[Cat Meows]
No, no.
Dear Mom--
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
- [ Yells ]
- [ Screams ]
Mr. Marshall !
Mr. Marshall ?
Yes, Erin.
Yes, it's me.
- [ Panting ]
- l'm sorry.
I really did not mean
to scare you. Okay ?
I just wanted to come
and see how you are.
How are you ?
Mr. Marshall, if you're here because
I didn't show up today, I'm sorry.
I was just about to call.
I swear.
No, I'm not here because
you didn't show up for work.
But I'm here--
Well, I--
I bet you're wondering
why I am here, huh ?
As a matter of fact,
I was just thinking that.
I was thinking, ''Why is Mr. Marshall
here in my bedroom ?''
You were...
thinking that just now ?
Yeah, in my head.
I must have water
in my ears or something.
But you're, you know,
not thinking anything now, are you ?
I'm thinking a million things.
Really ?
Because, you know,
usually I can, uh--
I can, uh--
You are thinking something
right this minute ?
Mr. Marshall, I am thinking
that you are crazier than I am.
I think--
I think I lost--
It's gone.
I'm back.
- I'm back.
- Mr. Marshall ?
Yeah ?
I'm sorry. Is there something
I can maybe do for you ?
No.
No, Erin, uh--
Actually, I came here to see if
I could do something for you.
- For me ?
- Yeah.
See, the truth is--
The truth--
Erin, the truth is,
I'm glad I got here before you
did anything to hurt yourself.
What makes you think that
I would, uh,
do something
to hurt myself?
I just sensed it.
Really ?
You could sense that ?
Well, that's not--
That's not good.
[Sobbing]
Yeah. But the real reason
I'm here is because--
Well, here's the thing. The real
reason I'm here is because--
As you know
we have the Nike account,
and we have a job opening
in our team.
And Darcy McGuire and I,
we were just discussing--
really spitballing on who could be
great enough to fill that void.
Suddenly, your name popped
into my head, and I remembered...
that you once applied
for a job as a copywriter.
I thought I'd come down here and
see if you were still interested.
Didn't you try and meet with me
a while back ?
Yeah, I tried, but you were
unavailable, and then out of town--
Well, now I'm available.
And as you can plainly see
I'm in town,
so I'm here
to take that meeting...
if you're available.
I'm available.
I'm unbelievably available.
[ Buzzing ]
[Dialing]
[ Ringing ]
[Darcy On Answering Machine]
Hi, this is Darcy McGuire.
l'm not home right now,
so please leave a message.
- I'll get back as soon as I can.
- [Beeps]
Darcy ?
Hi, Darcy, it's Nick.
Uh, l'm standing right outside
your place here.
I sure wish I could find you,
get a hold of you.
Are you all right ?
I hope so.
Anyway, call me
when you get this.
I'm on my cell.
Triple five, 1-2-2-6.
I really need to talk to you.
Uh--
Just making sure
you're not there.
You're not, right ?
No, I didn't think so.
All right, so call me, please.
Please.
Bye.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Darcy ?
- [ Gigi ] No, it's me.
Gigi ? Uh--
Is everything all right ?
- Are you back in town already ?
- No, not until tomorrow.
Alex called me three times
from a pay phone really upset.
Then we got disconnected. What's
the matter ? Isn't she at the prom ?
[ Sighs ]
The prom.
Excuse me. Do you know
where Alex Marshall is ?
Little tenth grader ?
Brown hair ? About this high ?
I saw her in the ladies' room.
She's been there for, like, an hour.
Alex, are you in here ?
[Alex Sobbing]
Alex, it's me.
[Scoffs]
What are you doing here ?
Oh, honey, I just--
You know, I can't believe
that I screwed up.
I wasn't there when
you left for the prom.
Yeah, well, that's not why l'm
in here, so you can just go, okay ?
Oh, boy, I feel awful.
Are you okay ? I mean, I--
Come on out. Let me see
how you look, at least.
- Come on.
- [Sobbing]I look like crap !
I already took my hair out
and everything.
So, you know,
what happened ?
Well, if I told you,
you'd just freak out, so--
What have you got to lose ?
Try me.
Okay.
Cameron and his friends,
they had this big plan.
They rented this hotelroom
and-and--
It was like a suite.
Basically, I promised him
that I was gonna--
I can't believe I'm gonna
say this to you. [Sniffles]
I promised him that
I was gonna...
sleep with him
after the prom.
And like an hour ago,
we were on the dance floor
and I said,
''I'm sorry, Cameron.
You know, I'm just not ready.''
Good.
Good girl.
- Dad, come on !
- l'm sorry, l'm sorry. Go on.
Then he goes, ''Well, the limo,
the room and the tux,
it all cost me 400 bucks. ''
And I said,
''I'm sorry. I'm just not--''
And he cuts me off
and he says,
''I never should've asked a sophomore
to the prom. What a waste.''
Then two seconds later,
he goes and meets up
with his old girlfriend...
and starts making out
with her.
I mean, this disgusting slut
with a tongue ring.
And then they were
laughing and--
I just can't
go out there ever.
- Oh, honey, l'm so proud of you.
- Dad !
- What are you doing ?
- I'm sorry. I'm-I'm sorry.
But I am.
And believe it or not,
I know what it's like
to be a woman.
I mean, it's not
as easy as it looks.
You stood up for yourself. You know
how ahead of the game you are ?
Anyway, a guy that treats you like
that and talks to you like that,
- he's not--
- Worth my time. Yes, I know.
- It's true. He's not.
- He's a gameplayer, I hate that.
You are so much smarter
than me.
And look at you.
That clown made out with a girl
with a tongue ring over you ?
Honey...
you look beautiful.
Thanks.
Take me home, Dad.
What am I doing ?
She's not in the refrigerator.
I wonder if it's too late
to go over there.
No, it's not too late. It's never
too late to do the right thing.
That's what I'll do. I'll go over
there and I'll do the right thing.
[lntercom Buzzing]
Hello ?
Uh, hi, it's me.
Oh, I'm glad I found you.
Uh--
Can I come up ?
Darcy ?
I need to--
[Door Buzzing]
Hey.
You need to what ?
It's 1:00 in the morning.
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Thanks.
So, you sleep here now ?
I thought I might as well give it a
try before I have to sell the place.
Sell it? You're not
selling the place.
Can't afford to keep it.
I don't have a job.
You know, you ought to try
returning some of your phone calls.
- You got your job back.
- Oh, do I ?
- You're a riot. You know that ?
- lt's true.
Dan told me so himself.
Why would he tell you that ? I
didn't do the job he hired me to do.
Even I don't blame him
for firing me.
Look, I'm, uh--
You can come on in.
I don't have any chairs,
but if you wanna--
What if I told you that...
you did everything
that you were hired to do--
everything-- but that
someone was sabotaging you ?
Picking your brain,
swiping your ideas and--
Well, you-- you never
even knew what hit you.
- How is that possible ?
- Oh, trust me, it's possible.
Well, who would do
such an awful thing ?
I would.
I was a dope
with a corner office.
And when you came with the job
I was supposed to have,
I mean, it didn't matter
to me that...
you were better at it than me
or you earned it more than I did.
As far as I was concerned, it was
mine, and I was gonna get it back.
So I took advantage of you
in the worst possible way.
Have you ever done that ?
Taken the wrong road and--
No, of course you haven't.
You wouldn't do that.
That's just--
Somebody like me does that.
And, uh--
The problem with that was that while
I was digging the hole under you...
I found out
all about you.
And the more I found out...
the more you dazzled me.
I mean, shook my world,
changed my life, dazzled me.
And guys like that ex-husband
of yours, he made you feel that...
the price you pay
just for being you...
is that you don't get
to have love.
Isn't that what you were
trying to say the other night ?
That you weren't complete ?
That you weren't really a winner ?
Everything about you--
how smart you are,
how good you are--
everything just makes me
want you even more.
Oh, wow.
Boy.
So it looks like I'm here
at 1:00 in the morning...
being all heroic
trying to rescue you,
but the truth is...
I'm the one that needs
to be rescued here.
I sure wish
I could read your mind.
Well, I was thinking that, um,
if everything you're saying
is true,
if I really have
my job back...
then I think you're fired.
Well, I never-- I never really
thought about it from that angle.
Well, not that
I don't deserve it. I-do-do--
I'm stuttering.
Now I feel kind of, uh,
embarrassed that I told you
I needed to be rescued.
But that's-that's fine.
That's it ?
I don't want that to be it.
I don't want that
to be it at all.
Then don't let a little thing like
me firing you stand in your way.
I didn't know
what to react to first.
Hey, news flash.
I took the wrong road.
What kind of knight
in shining armor would I be...
if the man I love
needs rescuing...
and I just let him
walk out my door ?
My hero.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org